ILR School "Voice of Ives Hall" and "ILR Voice" Publications /3073 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School "Voice of Ives Hall" and "ILR Voice" Publications
1963-1989
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/3073 PUBS
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Publications (documents).
Consists of issues from foour ILR School Publications: Consensus, For Our Information, Voice of Ives Hall, and ILR Voice.
1337043
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, January 26, 2015
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, February 22, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
1337043
- Consensus/Voice, Assorted Years (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Consensus (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Consensus Part 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Consensus, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- FOI (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Voice, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Voice, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Voice, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Voice, Part 1, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Voice, Part 2, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Voice, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Voice, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Voice, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Voice, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Voice, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Voice, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Voice, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Voice, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Voice, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Voice, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Voice, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Voice, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- 1987-89, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 23)